Mss.B.In6
American Philosophical Society
- Series VI. Graphic Materials
  - Illustrated Fish Boards, No. 1, undated; 6.0 items (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Illustrated Fish Boards, No. 2, undated; 9.0 items (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Illustrated Fish Boards, No. 3, undated; 6.0 items (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Illustrated Fish Boards, No. 4, undated; 9.0 items (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Illustrated Fish Boards, No. 5, undated; 6.0 items (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Plant Life Sketches, No. 1, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Plant Life Sketches, No. 2, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Plant Life Sketches, No. 3, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Plant Life Sketches, No. 4, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Plant Life Sketches, No. 5, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Pond Photographs, No. 1, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Pond Photographs, No. 2, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Pond Photographs, No. 3, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Pond Photographs, No. 4, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Pond Photographs, No. 5, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    A series of postcards illustrated with photos and drawings of fish.
  - Seahorse Photographs, undated; 9.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 12)
    Folder contains a series of still images from the film L'Hippocampe(1934) by director Jean Painleve.
  - Personal Photographs
    - "Bal. Cellar, 1945" (negative image), 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 13)
      Contains 6 photographic negatives.
    - "Chadwick Louis and Junior on our front step" (negative), undated; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - "Copy of Mary and Irene weber as Little Children" (negative image), undated; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - "Ektachromes of H. Serphae and Blue Lourai", undated; 2.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - "Evelyn, Mary, and Betty with Huckster Wagon, Canal St.", undated; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - "Family Looking in Aquarium, copied from LIFE and other magazines", undated; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - "A Few Western Negatives of 1929", 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - "Florida: November 1941, Family Trip", 1942; 14.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - "Figures on the Cover of Modern Aquarium", undated; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - "George Myers, 1944", 4.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - "The Goldfish Negative", undated; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - "Goldfish Spawning or Rise of Myriophyllum", undated; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Hand-drawn Envelope Addressed to William T. Innes (negative copy), 1946; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Joseph Baldwin Kirkbride (negatives), undated; 2.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - "Kirkbride Home in Bristol, PA", undated; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - "Mary-Jean, Meade, and Page at Ventura, NJ", undated; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - "Meridian Club Presidents", 1941; 2.0 Photograph(s) (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - "Moorestown Group Films, Thanksgiving, 1951", 3.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - "Mostly Enlarged Negatives from Motion Pictures, also Weber Grandparents", undated; 38.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Painted Portrait of William T. Innes, undated; 1.0 item (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Personal Photographs: Innes and Colleagues, No. 1, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Personal Photographs: Innes and Colleagues, No. 2, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Personal Photographs: Innes and Colleagues, No. 3, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Personal Photographs: Innes and Colleagues, No. 4, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Personal Photographs: Innes and Colleagues, No. 5, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Personal Photographs: Innes and Family, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Portrait of Willimam T. Innes, undated; 3.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - "Ruth and George Myers - Subject Used in a Magazine", undated; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - "Soldering Aquarium Frame", 1949; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - "Steve, Betsy, Julia, Claire, Larien, F.I.M., June, 1944", 1944 June; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - "Tilapia Sparrmanni", 1949; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Unlabeled Negatives (fish), undated; 8.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Unlabeled Negatives (family), No. 1, undated; 15.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Unlabeled Negatives (family), No. 2, undated; 15.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Unlabeled Negatives (family), No. 3, undated; 15.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Unlabeled Negatives (family), No. 4, 14.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Unlabeled Negatives (family), No. 5, undated; 18.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Unlabeled Negatives (family), No. 6, undated; 25.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Unlabeled Negatives (family), No. 7, undated; 12.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Unlabeled Negatives (family), No. 8, undated; 21.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Unlabeled Negatives (family), No. 9, undated; 17.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - "William T. Innes - Dressed as Benjamin Franklin", 1949 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - "William T. Innes - Fairmount Water Works", undated; 3.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - "William T. Innes - Photographed with His Equiptment", undated; 4.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - "William T. Innes - With His Equipment for Inquirer Spread", 1948; 16.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - "William T. Innes - Recieving Honorary Degree of Doctor of Humane Letters", 1951 February 15; 6.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - "Your Aquarium - Negative Cover Proof", undated; 2.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - "Zoo and Lt. Williams, and Junior, Backyard, Children Groups", undated; 22.0 Photograph(s) (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - William T. Innes - Portraits, undated
      William T. Innes - Portraits
      A brown paper package of headshots of William T. Innes.
    - "XIth Physiological Congress", 1923 July; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 29)
    - "Physiological Congress", undated; 1.0 Photograph(s) (Box 30)
    - Copper Printing Plates, undated; 2.0 items (Box 31)
      Copper Printing Plates
      Two copper printing plates, mounted on wood. Images show William T. Innes dressed as Benjamin Franklin.
  - Glass Plate Photographs, 8.0 boxes (1 ln. ft.)
    This subseries consists of 9 boxes of photgraphic glass plates.
    - Glass Plates, No. 1, 49.0 Photograph(s) (Box 32)
    - Glass Plates, No. 2, undated; 43.0 Photograph(s) (Box 33)
    - Glass Plates, No. 3, 1927 - 1948; 65.0 Photograph(s) (Box 34)
    - Glass Plates, No. 4, 1948 - 1950; 24.0 Photograph(s) (Box 35)
    - Glass Plates, No. 5, 1950 - 1956; 30.0 Photograph(s) (Box 36)
    - Glass Plates, No. 6, undated; 24.0 Photograph(s) (Box 37)
    - Glass Plates, No. 7, (personal photographs), 1897 - 1951; 30.0 Photograph(s) (Box 38)
    - Lantern Slides, undated; 26.0 Photograph(s) (Box 39)
    - Oversized Glass Plates, undated; 15.0 Photograph(s) (Box 40)
- Series VII. Miscellaneous Materials
  - Miscellaneous No. 1, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Miscellaneous No. 1
    Folder consists of various miscellaneous materials including: a certificate designating William T. Innes "a perpetual member of the St. Jude Apostolate," a guide book from the Eastman Kodak Company on "How to Expose Kodachrome," and a pamphlet titled, "Blackbeard: The Pirate in Philadelphia, 1717."
  - Miscellaneous No. 2, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Miscellaneous No. 2
    Miscellaneous materials. Seasonal cards, poems, and sample cover of Exotic Aquarium Fishes.
  - Miscellaneous No. 3, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
    Miscellaneous No. 3
    Newspaper clippings and invitations to various events.
  - Miscellaneous No. 4, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous No. 5, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
    Miscellaneous No. 5
    "Innes & Sons Printers" envelopes.
  - Miscellaneous No. 6, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
    Miscellaneous No. 6
    Blank fish cards with envelopes.
  - "Pioneers of Industry Award", 1950; 1.0 item (Box 41)
    Pioneers of Industry Award
    Awarded to William T. Innes by the Dobbins Vocational Technical School in Philadelphia.
  - Photographic Dry Plates, undated; 1.0 item (Box 42, Object 1)
    Photographic Dry Plates
    An empty box from the Hammer Dry Plate Company.
  - Opaque white Plates, undated; 2.0 items (Box 42, Object 2)
    Opaque White Plates
    Two plates presumably used by William T. Innes to photograph fish.
  - Shaw Walker wooden box, undated; 1.0 item (Box 42, Object 3)